<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet href="/feed_style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="https://www.rssboard.org/media-rss">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on evnmrk.xyz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on evnmrk.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><icon>http://localhost:1313/apple-touch-icon.png</icon>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One Year</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/one-year/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>September 14th, 2024, marks the first year of my blog. Since this website&rsquo;s inception, I have made four (4) posts. That is one post every 3 months, which is pretty terrible.</p>
<p>My idea for this blog has changed slightly since last year. Originally, I wanted to post anything that interested me, from computer science and cybersecurity topics to movie and music reviews. If you have not noticed, I only have the former on this website. I&rsquo;ve decided to focus solely on computer science/cybersecurity topics on this blog, using this space as a complement to my resume, to showcase my skills, experience, and interests.</p>
<p>Just because I haven&rsquo;t posted anything does not mean I was dormant this past year; some of my largest accomplishments were:</p>
<ul>
<li>Graduated from university in the Fall 2023 semester</li>
<li>Hired as a programmer/systems analyst for my county&rsquo;s Sheriff&rsquo;s Office</li>
<li>Completed the CompTIA Security+ certification</li>
</ul>
<p>I didn&rsquo;t post these on my blog because I was not sure how I wanted to present myself here. Staying (partly) pseudonymous was my original goal to stay private, but I think connecting my LinkedIn to this blog and creating my public image would help me in my future career. Having an anonymous or pseudonymous account to post one&rsquo;s accomplishments may not be useful if you cannot show your blog/account to a future employer. Some cybersecurity personalities that inspired me to make this change were <a href="https://www.troyhunt.com/">Troy Hunt</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@_JohnHammond">John Hammond</a>. I will still be shy in showing my face or location, but it is not too hard to find me.</p>
<p>As a sort of one year anniversary resolution, I want to challenge myself to <em><strong>post once every two weeks at the least.</strong></em> Some of my posts will be better than others; some will be more cybersecurity focused or computer science focused than others; and some will be more complex or interesting than others. James Clear, in his book <a href="https://jamesclear.com/atomic-habits"><em>Atomic Habits</em></a>, writes about the mantra &ldquo;Don&rsquo;t break the chain.&rdquo; In my context, writing a perfect or great post is not as important as just making a post for the two weeks. Just writing a post affirms that I am the type of person who consistently reflects on what I am learning, writes about it, and posts it online.</p>
<p>If this goal is consistently met by next year, I may switch to one post every week.</p>
<p>Here&rsquo;s to a more productive year,</p>
<p>Evan</p>
]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 20:00:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello world!</p>
<p>This is my first post marking the day I set up this website.</p>
<h2 id="purpose-of-this-blog">Purpose of This Blog</h2>
<p>I created this blog as a response to the gaining popularity of &ldquo;micro-blogging&rdquo; websites like Twitter and Facebook. Micro-blogging leaves little room for complete thoughts and ideas, and I believe personal blogs are the remedy to this problem. Plus, personal blogs can have much more customization if one knows their way around their static site generator.</p>
<p>Another reason for the existence of my blog is for me to begin writing and creating. My entire life has consisted of many consumptions but very little creations, and now that my college journey is coming to a close, I have noticed that I have very little projects or code to show to prospective employers or my peers; projects or code that I am proud of. Recently, I have read that creating gives one more pleasure than consuming, so I hope to begin writing frequently, perhaps an article every one to two weeks. This should also lead me to spend my free time learning something worth writing about while also improving my composition. Two birds, one stone.</p>
<h2 id="what-to-expect">What to Expect</h2>
<p>I plan to post about my interests. These include: code snippets, CTF write-ups, film and music reviews, random thoughts or ideas. I may even write some short stories or draw some quick digital art. Whatever I feel like creating, I will likely put here. If these topics interest you, feel free to bookmark this page or subscribe to the RSS feed to get notifications as soon as this site is updated.</p>
<p>Hopefully, in the near future, I will have a website full of work that I can be proud of.</p>
<p>If you want to contact me you can find my email at the <a href="http://localhost:1313/about/">about page</a>. I would love to hear your thoughts and opinions about my posts, or if you found any errors or typos.</p>
<p>Thank you for reading,</p>
<p>evnmrk</p>]]></description>
      
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
